astroved.com 2015-06-08

# AstroVed - Privacy Policy

Dear AstroVed Members,

At AstroVed we take online privacy and security concerns seriously. At the same time we are continuously working to make your AstroVed experience an entertaining, pleasant and satisfying one. To accomplish these goals we need to obtain some information from you when you use our site. This privacy policy will tell you how and when we collect information through our site and how this information will be used.

AstroVed.com collects information for internal use within the AstroVed business only. We will not sell, rent, or disclose any information related to you to any company outside AstroVed for such company’s own marketing or other commercial use, without obtaining your permission. 

We collect personal information from you through our web site only when: 1) you sign up with AstroVed as a member, 2) when you add other users under your membership, and 3) when you purchase products from AstroVed. 

### AstroVed Membership

When you sign up with AstroVed we will ask you to 1) provide your name, 2) create a user id and password, 3) provide email information, 4) provide your birth/gender information, 5) provide your current location information, 6) provide credit card information based on membership type selected. We will use your name for reporting purposes. If you decide to set up an online account with us, your user id and password will ensure that you are the only one who can access the account. However, it remains your responsibility to ensure no unauthorized access of your account. It is your responsibility to ensure that no minor is able to access your account.

We will use your email address to fulfill your requests for items such as general information, reports, and newsletters. We will use your gender, birth and current location information to provide you with the astrological reports and services you request. We require credit card information to complete your registration if you require a paid membership. 

### Adding Users Under Your Membership

For paid users AstroVed allow you to run reports on additional users you are interested in viewing astrological data for. For free memberships AstroVed will allow you to run reports on 1 additional user. In order to do this we need to collect their 1) name, 2) birth/gender information, 3) and current location information. All of this information will be used for reporting purposes.

### Purchasing from AstroVed

When you make a purchase from AstroVed, we will need to obtain personal information from you such as your address (billing as well as shipping address) along with your credit card information to complete the transaction and process your order. If you choose to create an online account with us, we will keep information related to your purchases, after your transaction is completed. This will make it easier for you to shop with us, because you will not need to submit transaction information each time. You can review this information at anytime via your online account, which will only be accessiable to you through your user-ID and password.

At AstroVed we are committed to creating high quality services and we are interested in building long-lasting relationships with our customers. Relationships are built on trust, so if you ever question what data has been collected or you may want to change personal information you may do so by accessing your online account anytime if you have registered with us. If you have any questions about the your online account or the information we have stored about you, please [Click Here](mailto:services@Astroved.com) to contact us
